Thomas Chester "Chet" Edwards State Legislative papers, Inclusive: 1957-1991, Bulk: 1982-1990.
Baylor University, Baylor Collections of Political Materials
- 69th Session, 1969-1988; 4
  - Topical, 1969-1988; 5
    - Criminal Justice, Texas Department of Corrections, General (1 of 2), 1985-1986 (Box 95, Folder 3)
    - Criminal Justice, Texas Department of Corrections, General (2 of 2), 1985-1986 (Box 95, Folder 4)
    - Criminal Justice, Texas Department of Corrections, Land Purchase and Construction, 1983-1986 (Box 95, Folder 5)
    - Criminal Justice, Texas Department of Corrections, Land Purchase and Construction News clippings, 1986 (Box 95, Folder 6)
    - Criminal Justice, Texas Department of Corrections, Meeting Notes, 1986 April 30 (Box 95, Folder 7)
    - Criminal Justice, Texas Department of Corrections, News clippings, 1985-1986 (Box 95, Folder 8)
    - Criminal Justice, Texas Department of Corrections, Newsletters, 1985-1986 (Box 95, Folder 9)
    - Criminal Justice, Texas Department of Corrections, Notes, 1985-1986 (Box 95, Folder 10)
    - Criminal Justice, Texas Department of Corrections, Other States, 1980-1985 (Box 95, Folder 11)
    - Criminal Justice, Texas Department of Corrections, Policies and Programs, 1982-1987 (Box 95, Folder 12)
    - Criminal Justice, Texas Department of Corrections, Population file, 1987 (Box 95, Folder 13)
    - Criminal Justice, Texas Department of Corrections, Practices and Procedures, 1986 (Box 95, Folder 14)
    - Criminal Justice, Texas Department of Corrections, Prison Reform Sullivan article, undated (Box 95, Folder 15)
    - Criminal Justice, Texas Department of Corrections, Quorum Report, undated (Box 95, Folder 16)
    - Criminal Justice, Texas Department of Corrections, Sunset Advisory Commission Review, 1985 (Box 96, Folder 1)
    - Criminal Justice, Texas Department of Corrections, Sunset Staff Evaluation, 1977-1986 (Box 96, Folder 2)
    - Criminal Justice, Texas Department of Corrections, Review of Corrections, 1986 (Box 96, Folder 3)
    - Criminal Justice, Victims Assistance Information, 1984-1986 (Box 96, Folder 4)
    - Criminal Justice, Victims’ Rights notes, 1985, undated (Box 96, Folder 5)
    - District Maps, 1982-1986 (Box 96, Folder 6)
    - Drinking Age and Traffic Fatalities, 1985 (Box 96, Folder 7)
    - DWI, 1985-1986 (Box 96, Folder 8)
    - Education, Higher Education, 1986 (Box 96, Folder 9)
    - Education, Public Education, 1984-1986 (Box 96, Folder 10)
    - Education, Robinson ISD Performance and Budget, 1985-1987 (Box 96, Folder 11)
    - Education, Teacher Training, 1985 (Box 96, Folder 12)
    - Education, TSTI Budget and Funding Notes (1 of 2), 1981-1987 (Box 96, Folder 13)
    - Education, TSTI Budget and Funding Notes (2 of 2), 1981-1987 (Box 96, Folder 14)
    - Education, TSTI Select Committee on Higher Education (1 of 2), 1986 (Box 97, Folder 1)
    - Education, TSTI Select Committee on Higher Education (2 of 2), 1986 (Box 97, Folder 2)
    - Election Code, Presidential Primary (1 of 2), 1986 (Box 97, Folder 3)
    - Election Code, Presidential Primary (2 of 2), 1986 (Box 97, Folder 4)
    - Election Code, Report, Volume II, 1985 February (Box 97, Folder 5)
    - Environmental, Air Control, 1986 (Box 97, Folder 6)
    - Environmental, Air Pollution Control, 1985 (Box 97, Folder 7)
    - Falls County, Various District Information, 1985-1986 (Box 97, Folder 8)
    - General, 1985-1986 (Box 97, Folder 9)
    - Grand Jury Reform, Clippings, 1986 (Box 97, Folder 10)
    - Grant Projects: Limestone County, 1985 (Box 97, Folder 11)
    - Grant Projects: Navarro County, 1986 (Box 97, Folder 12)
    - Health, ABC News Nightline Transcripts, Board of Medical Examiners, 1986 (Box 98, Folder 1)
    - Health, Budget Information, Board of Medical Examiners, undated (Box 98, Folder 2)
    - Health, Children with Disabilities, 1986 (Box 98, Folder 3)
    - Health, Discipline, Board of Medical Examiners, 1986, undated (Box 98, Folder 4)
    - Health, Eastern Medicine, 1984 (Box 98, Folder 5)
    - Health, Health Care Costs, 1984-1985 (Box 98, Folder 6)
    - Health, Hospital Data Advisory Committee, 1986 October (Box 98, Folder 7)
    - Health, Indigent Health Care: Notes and Articles, 1985 (Box 98, Folder 8)
    - Health, Joan’s Notes, Board of Medical Examiners, 1986, undated (Box 98, Folder 9)
    - Health, Long Term Care Standards, 1981-1984, undated (Box 98, Folder 10)
    - Health, Malpractice Statistical Reports, Board of Medical Examiners, 1987 (Box 98, Folder 11)
    - Health, University of Texas Health Science Center at Houston School of Nursing, 1985-1986 (Box 98, Folder 12)
    - Health and Human Resources, 1984, undated (Box 98, Folder 13)
    - Health and Human Resources, Crippled Children’s Services, 1986 (Box 98, Folder 14)
    - Health and Human Resources, Opticianry, 1984 (Box 99, Folder 1)
    - Health and Human Services, Annual Report, 1985 (Box 99, Folder 2)
    - Health and Human Services, Child Care, 1983-1986 (Box 99, Folder 3)
    - Health and Human Services, Coordinating Committee, 1984-1986 (Box 99, Folder 4)
    - Health and Human Services, Elderly and Youth, 1985 (Box 99, Folder 5)
    - Health and Human Services, Disability (1 of 2), 1984-1986 (Box 99, Folder 6)
    - Health and Human Services, Disability (2 of 2), 1984-1986 (Box 99, Folder 7)
    - Health and Human Services, Disabilities Demographic Survey, 1986 (Box 99, Folder 8)
    - Health and Human Services, Genetic Screening, 1985-1986 (Box 99, Folder 9)
    - Health and Human Services, Health Prevention, 1986 (Box 99, Folder 10)
    - Health and Human Services, Long Term Care Administrative Penalties, Responses (1 of 2), 1985-1986 (Box 99, Folder 11)
    - Health and Human Services, Long Term Care Administrative Penalties, Responses (2 of 2), 1985-1986 (Box 100, Folder 1)
    - Health and Human Services, Long Term Care Administrative Penalties (1 of 2), 1985-1986 (Box 100, Folder 2)
    - Health and Human Services, Long Term Care Administrative Penalties (2 of 2), 1985-1986 (Box 100, Folder 3)
    - Health and Human Services, Long Term Care Administrative Penalties, 1985, undated (Box 100, Folder 4)
    - Health and Human Services, Long Term Care and Disability, 1986 (Box 100, Folder 5)
    - Health and Human Services, Nursing Home Care, 1985-1986 (Box 100, Folder 6)
    - Health and Human Services, Nursing Home Administrative Penalties, 1985-1986 (Box 100, Folder 7)
    - High Technology, $35 million Advanced Technology Research Program Award, 1985-1986 (Box 100, Folder 8)
    - High Technology, Advisory Committee Reports (1 of 2), 1984 (Box 101, Folder 1)
    - High Technology, Advisory Committee Reports (2 of 2), 1984 (Box 101, Folder 2)
    - High Technology, Agriculture and Food, 1985 (Box 101, Folder 3)
    - High Technology, Association of Higher Education of North Texas, 1980-1986 (Box 101, Folder 4)
    - High Technology, Attracting High Tech, 1984, undated (Box 101, Folder 5)
    - High Technology, Attracting High Tech Industry in Texas, 1984 (Box 101, Folder 6)
    - High Technology, Basic Research and Research Development, 1984 (Box 101, Folder 7)
    - High Technology, Biotechnology, 1984-1986 (Box 101, Folder 8)
    - High Technology, Benefits and Testimonies, 1984-1985, undated (Box 101, Folder 9)
    - High Technology, Brochures and Magazines, 1983-1984 (Box 101, Folder 10)
    - High Technology, Commercialization, News clippings and Articles, 1984 (Box 101, Folder 11)
    - High Technology, Committee on Business, Technology, and Education, 1984 April 9 (Box 101, Folder 12)
    - High Technology, Committee on Business, Technology, and Education, Tape Transcripts, 1984 July 13 (Box 102, Folder 1)
    - High Technology, Committee on Business, Technology, and Education, Tape Transcripts, 1984 June 6 (Box 102, Folder 2)
    - High Technology, Committee Script, 1984 April 9 (Box 102, Folder 3)
    - High Technology, Computer Software, 1984 (Box 102, Folder 4)
    - High Technology, Computers in the Classroom, 1983-1984 (Box 102, Folder 5)
    - High Technology, Conference on Venture Capital, 1986 (Box 102, Folder 6)
    - High Technology, Contacts, 1986 (Box 102, Folder 7)
    - High Technology, Economic Climate, News clippings and Articles, 1983-1984 (Box 102, Folder 8)
    - High Technology, Economic Diversification, 1984-1986 (Box 102, Folder 9)
    - High Technology, Economic Growth and Development, News clippings and Magazines, 1983-1984 (Box 102, Folder 10)
    - High Technology, Education and the Economy, 1983-1985 (Box 102, Folder 11)
    - High Technology, Edwards Press Conference, 1987 March (Box 102, Folder 12)
    - High Technology, Elementary and Secondary Education articles, 1983-1984 (Box 102, Folder 13)
    - High Technology, Employment, 1983-1986 (Box 102, Folder 14)
    - High Technology, Employment Forecast, 1983-1984 (Box 103, Folder 1)
    - High Technology, Entrepreneurship, 1983 (Box 103, Folder 2)
    - High Technology, Europe, 1984 (Box 103, Folder 3)
    - High Technology, Federal Agencies and Commissions — NASA, 1984 (Box 103, Folder 4)
    - High Technology, Foreign Trade Zone, 1983-1984 (Box 103, Folder 5)
    - High Technology, General, 1983-1984 (Box 103, Folder 6)
    - High Technology, General, 1983-1985 (Box 103, Folder 7)
    - High Technology, General, 1984 (Box 103, Folder 8)
    - High Technology, General, 1986, undated (Box 103, Folder 9)
    - High Technology, General Handwritten Notes, undated (Box 103, Folder 10)
    - High Technology, General News clippings and Articles, 1983-1984 (Box 103, Folder 11)
    - High Technology, General News clippings and Articles, 1984 (Box 103, Folder 12)
    - High Technology, Geo Technology Installation, 1985 (Box 103, Folder 13)
    - High Technology, Hazardous Waste, 1984 (Box 103, Folder 14)
    - High Technology, Hazardous Waste, 1985-1986 (Box 103, Folder 15)
    - High Technology, House Interim Subcommittee, 1984 September 24 (Box 103, Folder 16)
    - High Technology, IC2 Institute, UT Austin, 1984-1986 (Box 103, Folder 17)
    - High Technology, Industrial Revenue Bonds, 1983, undated (Box 103, Folder 18)
    - High Technology, Information, 1983-1986 (Box 104, Folder 1)
    - High Technology, Institute for Ventures in Technology (INVENT), 1984 (Box 104, Folder 2)
    - High Technology, Interim Committee Information binder, 1983, undated (Box 104, Folder 3)
    - High Technology, International Trade, 1984-1986 (Box 104, Folder 4)
    - High Technology, Japan, 1983-1984 (Box 104, Folder 5)
    - High Technology, Job Market (1 of 2), 1982-1983 (Box 104, Folder 6)
    - High Technology, Job Market (2 of 2), 1982-1983 (Box 104, Folder 7)
    - High Technology, Jobs and Training, 1983-1984 (Box 104, Folder 8)
    - High Technology, Locations, 1982-1984 (Box 104, Folder 9)
    - High Technology, Mayoral Development Plans, 1984 (Box 104, Folder 10)
    - High Technology, The Mayor’s Task Force on High Technology, Dallas, 1984 May (Box 104, Folder 11)
    - High Technology, Megatrends Conference, undated (Box 104, Folder 12)
    - High Technology, Metroplex 2000: A Challenge for the Technology Committee, 1984 March 29-30 (Box 104, Folder 13)
    - High Technology, Microchips/VLSI, 1983-1984 (Box 105, Folder 1)
    - High Technology, Microelectronics and Computer Technology Corp. (MCC), 1983-1984 (Box 105, Folder 2)
    - High Technology, Need for Industrial and Economic Policy, 1984-1985 (Box 105, Folder 3)
    - High Technology, North Carolina Board of Science and Technology, 1984 (Box 105, Folder 4)
    - High Technology, Oil and Taxes, 1982-1984 (Box 105, Folder 5)
    - High Technology, Organized Research in Texas, 1982 (Box 105, Folder 6)
    - High Technology, Other States’ Programs — Arkansas, 1983-1984 (Box 105, Folder 7)
    - High Technology, Other States’ Programs — California, 1983-1986 (Box 105, Folder 8)
    - High Technology, Other States’ Programs — Florida, 1982-1983 (Box 105, Folder 9)
    - High Technology, Other States’ Programs — Georgia, 1983 (Box 105, Folder 10)
    - High Technology, Other States’ Programs — Illinois, 1983 (Box 105, Folder 11)
    - High Technology, Other States’ Programs — Iowa, 1983 (Box 105, Folder 12)
    - High Technology, Other States’ Programs — Maryland, 1983 (Box 105, Folder 13)
    - High Technology, Other States’ Programs — Michigan, 1982-1986 (Box 105, Folder 14)
    - High Technology, Other States’ Programs — Minnesota, 1983-1984 (Box 105, Folder 15)
    - High Technology, Other States’ Programs — Missouri, 1984 (Box 105, Folder 16)
    - High Technology, Other States’ Programs — Montana, 1984 (Box 105, Folder 17)
    - High Technology, Other States’ Programs — New Mexico (1 of 2), 1982 (Box 105, Folder 18)
    - High Technology, Other States’ Programs — New Mexico (2 of 2), 1982 (Box 105, Folder 19)
    - High Technology, Other States’ Programs — New Jersey, 1983 (Box 105, Folder 20)
    - High Technology, Other States’ Programs — New York, 1983, undated (Box 105, Folder 21)
    - High Technology, Other States’ Programs — North Carolina, 1983-1985 (Box 105, Folder 22)
    - High Technology, Other States’ Programs — Ohio, 1984 (Box 106, Folder 1)
    - High Technology, Other States’ Programs — Oklahoma, 1983 (Box 106, Folder 2)
    - High Technology, Other States’ Programs — Oregon, 1984 (Box 106, Folder 3)
    - High Technology, Other States’ Programs — Pennsylvania, 1982-1984 (Box 106, Folder 4)
    - High Technology, Other States’ Programs — Rhode Island, 1984 (Box 106, Folder 5)
    - High Technology, Other States’ Programs — Tennessee, 1982-1984 (Box 106, Folder 6)
    - High Technology, Other States’ Programs — Virginia, 1983-1984 (Box 106, Folder 7)
    - High Technology, Other States’ Programs — Wisconsin, 1984 (Box 106, Folder 8)
    - High Technology, The Private Sector/University Technology Alliance, 1984 (Box 106, Folder 9)
    - High Technology, Professional Education, 1983-1984 (Box 106, Folder 10)
    - High Technology, Professional Services, 1983 (Box 106, Folder 11)
    - High Technology, Public Texas Higher Education, 1983, undated (Box 106, Folder 12)
    - High Technology, Robotics, 1984, undated (Box 106, Folder 13)
    - High Technology, Science and Technology Committee notes, 1983-1985 (Box 106, Folder 14)
    - High Technology, Securities Law — Full Disclosure vs. Merit Review (1 of 2), 1984-1986 (Box 106, Folder 15)
    - High Technology, Securities Law — Full Disclosure vs. Merit Review (2 of 2), 1984-1986 (Box 106, Folder 16)
    - High Technology, Senate Committee on Business, Technology, and Education, 1983-1985 (Box 106, Folder 17)
    - High Technology, Senate Committee on Business, Technology, and Education, 1983-1984 (Box 106, Folder 18)
    - High Technology, Session Accomplishments, 1987 (Box 106, Folder 19)
    - High Technology, Small Business, 1983, undated (Box 107, Folder 1)
    - High Technology, Small Business High Technology Institute Conference, 1983 (Box 107, Folder 2)
    - High Technology, Southern Methodist University, 1984 (Box 107, Folder 3)
    - High Technology, Southwest Research Institute, Annual Report, 1984 (Box 107, Folder 4)
    - High Technology, Special Interim Committee on Science, Technology, and Education, 1983 December 7 (Box 107, Folder 5)
    - High Technology, State Trends, 1984-1986 (Box 107, Folder 6)
    - High Technology, State Trends, 1984-1985 (Box 107, Folder 7)
    - High Technology, Summary and Accomplishments, 1986 (Box 107, Folder 8)
    - High Technology, Superconducting Supercollider (SSC) (1 of 2), 1983-1985 (Box 107, Folder 9)
    - High Technology, Superconducting Supercollider (SSC) (2 of 2), 1983-1985 (Box 107, Folder 10)
    - High Technology, SSC Reports and Correspondence, 1983 (Box 107, Folder 11)
    - High Technology, TARGET ’90 Commission: Goals for San Antonio, 1984 (Box 107, Folder 12)
    - High Technology, Tax and Economy, Notes and Clippings, 1983-1984 (Box 107, Folder 13)
    - High Technology, Taxes and High Tech, 1983-1986 (Box 108, Folder 1)
    - High Technology, “Technology and Growth: State Initiatives in Technological Innovation”, 1983 (Box 108, Folder 2)
    - High Technology, Technology and the University, undated (Box 108, Folder 3)
    - High Technology, Technology Industry Legislative Task Force, 1985-1987 (Box 108, Folder 4)
    - High Technology, Technology Training Information Booklet (1 of 2), 1986, undated (Box 108, Folder 5)
    - High Technology, Technology Training Information Booklet (2 of 2), 1986, undated (Box 108, Folder 6)
    - High Technology, Texas A&M University Programs, 1983-1984 (Box 108, Folder 7)
    - High Technology, Texas A&M University Programs, 1985-1986 (Box 108, Folder 8)
    - High Technology, Texas Agricultural Experiment Station, 1983-1984 (Box 108, Folder 9)
    - High Technology, Texas Alliance for the Next Economy (TEXANE), 1986 (Box 108, Folder 10)
    - High Technology, Texas Business Review, 1983 March-August (Box 108, Folder 11)
    - High Technology, Texas Business Review, 1983 September-December (Box 109, Folder 1)
    - High Technology, Texas Colleges and Universities, Research Funding, 1983-1984, undated (Box 109, Folder 2)
    - High Technology, Texas Computer Industry Council, 1984 (Box 109, Folder 3)
    - High Technology, Texas Engineering Experiment Station, 1983-1984 (Box 109, Folder 4)
    - High Technology, Texas Engineering Experiment Station, 1983-1985 (Box 109, Folder 5)
    - High Technology, Texas Industrial Overview, undated (Box 109, Folder 6)
    - High Technology, Texas National Research Laboratory Commission, 1986 (Box 109, Folder 7)
    - High Technology, Texas Regional Activity articles, 1983-1984 (Box 109, Folder 8)
    - High Technology, Texas Regional Activity: Dallas, 1983-1984 (Box 109, Folder 9)
    - High Technology, Texas Regional Activity: Houston, 1984-1986 (Box 109, Folder 10)
    - High Technology, Texas Regional Activity, News clippings and Magazine Articles, 1984-1986 (Box 109, Folder 11)
    - High Technology, Texas Regional Activity: San Antonio, 1984-1985 (Box 109, Folder 12)
    - High Technology, Texas Science and Technology Council, 1986 (Box 109, Folder 13)
    - High Technology, Texas Tech University, Division of Japanese Studies, 1983-1984 (Box 109, Folder 14)
    - High Technology, University and Business Interaction, 1984, undated (Box 109, Folder 15)
    - High Technology, University Research, 1982-1984 (Box 109, Folder 16)
    - High Technology, University of Texas at Dallas, 1983 (Box 109, Folder 17)
    - High Technology, Venture Capital, 1983-1984 (Box 109, Folder 18)
    - High Technology, Women and Minorities in Engineering, 1984-1985 (Box 109, Folder 19)
    - Highways, Highways and Roads, 1985-1986 (Box 110, Folder 1)
    - Highways: Hill County Projects, 1986 (Box 110, Folder 2)
    - Highways: McLennan County Projects, 1985-1987 (Box 110, Folder 3)
    - Industry, Saturn Proposal, 1985 (Box 110, Folder 4)
    - Insurance Crisis, 1986 (Box 110, Folder 5)
    - Local Measured Service, Articles, 1982-1985 (Box 110, Folder 6)
    - Local Measured Service, Complaints and Support, 1984-1986 (Box 110, Folder 7)
    - Local Measured Service, Complaints and Support, 1984-1988 (Box 110, Folder 8)
    - Local Measured Service, Complaints, News clippings, 1985-1986 (Box 110, Folder 9)
    - Local Measured Service, Consumers Union, 1984-1986 (Box 110, Folder 10)
    - Local Measured Service, Dr. Lee Selwyn, 1981-1984 (Box 110, Folder 11)
    - Local Measured Service, Economics and Technology, Inc., 1984 (Box 110, Folder 12)
    - Local Measured Service, Edwards’s Notes, 1985, undated (Box 110, Folder 13)
    - Local Measured Service, Edwards's Statement and Notes, 1984-1985 (Box 110, Folder 14)
    - Local Measured Service, Edwards’s Questions for Southwestern Bell, undated (Box 110, Folder 15)
    - Local Measured Service, General Information, 1984, undated (Box 110, Folder 16)
    - Local Measured Service, General Information, 1979-1986 (Box 110, Folder 17)
    - Local Measured Service, Information Packet, 1979-1985 (Box 110, Folder 18)
    - Local Measured Service, Local Measured Service and S.B.6 News clippings, 1985-1986 (Box 110, Folder 19)
    - Local Measured Service, Media Coverage News clippings, 1984-1986 (Box 111, Folder 1)
    - Local Measured Service, Multi-Part Study, Economics and Technology, Inc., 1984 October (Box 111, Folder 2)
    - Local Measured Service, National Federation of Independent Business, 1983-1985 (Box 111, Folder 3)
    - Local Measured Service, Opposition to Southwestern Bell’s Proposal, undated (Box 111, Folder 4)
    - Local Measured Service, Other States’ Info: Alabama, 1986 (Box 111, Folder 5)
    - Local Measured Service, Other States’ Info: Alaska, 1986 (Box 111, Folder 6)
    - Local Measured Service, Other States’ Info: Arizona, 1986 (Box 111, Folder 7)
    - Local Measured Service, Other States’ Info: Arkansas, 1986 (Box 111, Folder 8)
    - Local Measured Service, Other States’ Info: California, 1986 (Box 111, Folder 9)
    - Local Measured Service, Other States’ Info: Colorado, 1986 (Box 111, Folder 10)
    - Local Measured Service, Other States’ Info: Connecticut, 1986 (Box 111, Folder 11)
    - Local Measured Service, Other States’ Info: Delaware, 1986 (Box 111, Folder 12)
    - Local Measured Service, Other States’ Info: Florida (1 of 2), 1986 (Box 111, Folder 13)
    - Local Measured Service, Other States’ Info: Florida (2 of 2), 1986 (Box 112, Folder 1)
    - Local Measured Service, Other States’ Info: Georgia, 1986 (Box 112, Folder 2)
    - Local Measured Service, Other States’ Info: Hawaii, 1986 (Box 112, Folder 3)
    - Local Measured Service, Other States’ Info: Idaho, 1986 (Box 112, Folder 4)
    - Local Measured Service, Other States’ Info: Illinois, 1986 (Box 112, Folder 5)
    - Local Measured Service, Other States’ Info: Indiana, 1986 (Box 112, Folder 6)
    - Local Measured Service, Other States’ Info: Iowa, 1986 (Box 112, Folder 7)
    - Local Measured Service, Other States’ Info: Kansas, 1986 (Box 112, Folder 8)
    - Local Measured Service, Other States’ Info: Kentucky, 1986 (Box 112, Folder 9)
    - Local Measured Service, Other States’ Info: Louisiana, 1986 (Box 112, Folder 10)
    - Local Measured Service, Other States’ Info: Maine (1 of 4), 1986 (Box 112, Folder 11)
    - Local Measured Service, Other States’ Info: Maine (2 of 4), 1986 (Box 112, Folder 12)
    - Local Measured Service, Other States’ Info: Maine (3 of 4), 1986 (Box 112, Folder 13)
    - Local Measured Service, Other States’ Info: Maine (4 of 4), 1986 (Box 113, Folder 1)
    - Local Measured Service, Other States’ Info: Maryland, 1986 (Box 113, Folder 2)
    - Local Measured Service, Other States’ Info: Massachusetts, 1986 (Box 113, Folder 3)
    - Local Measured Service, Other States’ Info: Mississippi, 1986 (Box 113, Folder 4)
    - Local Measured Service, Other States’ Info: Michigan, 1986 (Box 113, Folder 5)
    - Local Measured Service, Other States’ Info: Missouri, 1987 (Box 113, Folder 6)
    - Local Measured Service, Other States’ Info: Montana, 1986 (Box 113, Folder 7)
    - Local Measured Service, Other States’ Info: Nebraska, 1986 (Box 113, Folder 8)
    - Local Measured Service, Other States’ Info: Nevada, 1986 (Box 113, Folder 9)
    - Local Measured Service, Other States’ Info: New Hampshire, 1986 (Box 113, Folder 10)
    - Local Measured Service, Other States’ Info: New Jersey, 1986 (Box 113, Folder 11)
    - Local Measured Service, Other States’ Info: New Mexico, 1986 (Box 113, Folder 12)
    - Local Measured Service, Other States’ Info: New York, 1986 (Box 113, Folder 13)
    - Local Measured Service, Other States’ Info: New York, 1982-1986 (Box 113, Folder 14)
    - Local Measured Service, Other States’ Info: North Carolina (1 of 2), 1984-1986 (Box 113, Folder 15)
    - Local Measured Service, Other States’ Info: North Carolina (2 of 2), 1984-1986 (Box 113, Folder 16)